My God, save us!
What is this?
How terrifying!
He's coming!
Sister Clara?
What's happening?
Don't let the devil get to you!
Matthew 26:41.
Watch and pray.
So that you may not fall into temptation.
The spirit is willing,
but the flesh is weak.
Prayer is our only weapon
against the forces of darkness.
In times of your weakness,
the devil will visit
and play with you.
Prayer,
penance,
and sacrifice.
These are your weapons.
Fight against sin,
the weakness of the flesh,
and the seven deadly sins which are,
pride,
envy,
gluttony,
sloth,
lust,
wrath
and greed.
Cleanse your soul.
Otherwise,
the darkness will come upon you.
Sister Rosa?
My apologies, Sister Piedad.
What's this? Where did you get it?
The workers brought it from the pier.
Maybe…
it's a donation for the convent
from the sunken galleon.
A donation?
Or maybe it is trash from Mexico?
Sister Rosa?
Come here. Open this.
The devil has come!
Listen to me!
He is here!
Let me go!
The devil has come!
He is here! The devil has come!
I'm Ana. What's your name?
Flor.
Who are you looking for?
My older sister, Clara.
You have a sister here in the convent?
You're both lucky.
You two serve our God.
Is your sister the reason why you're here?
This is my punishment from my father
when he found out that my boyfriend
and I were going to elope.
That's forbidden!
Hide it! We might get scolded.
I'm sorry.
But whenever I feel sad or scared,
I get hungry.
Mother of God!
Do you know the punishment
for a sinful tongue?
Lifelong silence.
Listen to me!
The devil has come!
My Lord, I won't take what's not mine.
I will just take a look.
I am certain that
the voice I heard was Clara's.
Something is not right.
My sister Clara hasn't written
to me for a long time.
Whatever happened to her,
this might be the reason.
Sisters, can you accompany me
to look for my sister?
I cannot force you.
Sister, wait!
It is time for dinner.
Lastly,
be strong in your fight
so that you may be able
to fight the schemes of the devil
because our enemies are not humans.
Where is Sister Piedad?
-I haven't seen her since vespers ended.
-But against the powers…
The rulers of darkness
that exist in this world.
Clara!
Clara, what happened to you?
Why do you look like this?
-What did they do to you?
-Sister Flor, please.
The body is imprisoned,
but not the spirit.
Who?
Who, Clara?
There are shadows…
whispering.
-Vow of silence!
-They are playing with us.
Clara, what? What are you talking about?
You are disturbing the peace
of the evening meal!
Go back inside!
What have you done to my sister?
How barbaric!
Are they hurting you?
What are they doing to you?
What are they making you drink?
Are they poisoning you?
You are forbidden to eat tonight!
-Clara!
-You are forbidden to eat tonight!
Wait, I just want to speak
to my sister! Clara!
Clara!
Sister Piedad is still missing.
I wonder where she is.
Maybe she's in the chapel
or in the oratory.
Does the darkness frighten you, sister?
The thing you should fear more is
the punishment that awaits you.
What have you done to my sister?
Let me out!
Let me out of here!
Clara!
You need to learn.
Following orders is the path to holiness.
Clara, what will happen to me
when you leave?
Who will be my strength?
You don't need me to be strong, Flor.
You're brave.
You have your own inner strength.
One day, you'll be
someone else’s strength.
Flor.
Bring someone with you.
Bury her at the back.
This may be what Sister Clara meant.
-The devil is here!
-Be silent!
No one should know about this.
But Mother Juana?
Clara's visions caused this.
The devil is using her to frighten us.
But we will not be defeated.
We should pray harder.
Yes, Mother Superior.
Find someone to help you
bury Sister Piedad before dawn.
-Hurry up!
-Yes, Mother Juana.
Juana.
Come here. Open this.
Oh my God.
Your brother's missing ship
has already been found.
It's docked, and he's alive.
Thank you very much, Sister Clara.
Thank you very much.
Sister Clara, my body is aching.
Did you hear that?
I think someone is following us.
Do not speak of it.
If you speak of it, it will become real.
Do whatever you want.
I do not want trouble.
Salve!
What was that?
Who broke it?
It wasn't me.
Was it you again, Sister Ana?
Clean it.
Clean it!
Use your mouth.
What?
What did you say?
Do not make me repeat what I said.
This is unjust!
What do you know
about justice, Sister Flor?
You are here to be molded.
Not to ask questions.
I will do it.
What are you hiding from us?
I brought something
to get rid of the taste of soil.
I am just celebrating the life
that was given to me.
Is it your birthday, Sister Salve?
Yes.
Can I have some?
Sister Flor?
No, thank you.
I hope you can find a way
to leave this place,
and live the life you are dreaming of.
I know Clara will not forsake me.
I need to find her.
Sister!
Sister Flor!
Sister Salve!
Come here and look at this!
They died one after another.
Someone was just buried recently.
They are here, Mother Superior!
Not only did you steal from the kitchen,
but you also went against the rule
of not going to the back of the convent.
Watch them.
This is what will save you.
This will remind you not to commit sin.
This will cleanse your souls.
Please take away, my Lord,
what is troubling my spirit.
They have sinned.
They deserve to be punished.
I am not the bad one.
Is this my reward, O Lord?
The eclipse will devour the moon.
But the devil will eat the eclipse.
Then he will reign over the world.
Where did they take Rita's body?
Maybe they already sent her back
to her family.
Did she commit suicide because of us?
She was weak.
She couldn't handle the fact
that we were punished
because she reported us.
What was that?
Let's get out of here!
Wait! I'll join you in a bit.
I need to find my sister.
Sister Flor!
Come with me!
Sister Salve?
Where are you?
Salve, don't leave me!
Ana?
Don't leave me here, Salve!
Merciful God!
Get inside! Return to your rooms!
Lock the doors
and stay inside no matter what!
Hurry! Over there!
Clara, where are you?
You will not survive!
I am not afraid of you, Rita!
There is no way out!
You will not survive!
Salve, don't leave me!
Salve!
Clara?
Devil…
The devil!
Clara! Clara, this is me, Flor!
Hail Mary, full of grace,
the Lord is with thee.
Clara! Clara, it is me, Flor!
Clara!
Blessed art thou among women, and blessed
is the fruit of thy womb, Jesus…
Clara.
Flor?
Forgive me.
Clara.
What did they do to you?
What did Mother Juana do to you?
We need to stop the evil one.
What is happening?
The only thing I know comes solely
from my visions.
A creature of darkness,
born into this world
from a distant land
as old as time.
Cursed.
It spread terror and death.
Imprisoned by our family's ancestors
in a special chest.
But its spirit remained free.
Searching for sacrifices,
using our weaknesses and fears.
With every drop of blood,
and every soul consumed,
it gains the strength to be freed
and eradicate humanity.
The two of you!
You are the ones
who brought the devil here!
Servants of the devil!
Not us, Mother Juana. It was you!
Because of your fear, you imprisoned me.
You buried the truth within me!
And that is what gave the devil strength!
Shameless!
Mother Juana, fight back!
You have a good heart.
You have a light within you.
You can overcome this!
Mother Juana!
Enough!
Get out now!
Sister Josefa!
Mother Juana!
Mother Juana, stop it!
Clara!
-Clara!
-Flor! Go now! Quickly!
Clara.
-Run!
-Salve!
Mother Juana!
Clara!
Malum!
Clara, that is not the way out!
You need to be brave, Flor.
Clara.
What is that?
Clara?
Clara!
Leave now, Flor!
Save yourself!
I will not leave you!
O nails of the cross
of our Lord Jesus Christ,
fasten me to You, Lord,
in everlasting love!
O nails of the cross
of our Lord Jesus Christ,
fasten me to You, Lord,
in everlasting love!
Flor, leave now!
No!
Save your child!
No.
I will not leave you.
O nails of the cross
of our Lord Jesus Christ,
fasten me to You, Lord,
in everlasting love!
Flor.
What's up?
Girl!
You're overreacting.
I wasn't ready for your final look, dear.
-Right?
-Let me see.
She mothered! You're unbelievable!
Open the door. How does this work?
-Girl, it's amazing.
-Wow! Sky.
Looks real, Sky!
Faye, I told you
we'll get a big win tonight.
-It's so cool!
-I'll take a picture of you there.
Here it goes!
What will I pay them with?
I don't have any money.
Wow! It's beautiful!
-Sky, they did a good job.
-Wait, I'll take a picture.
-Let's take a picture here. Quick!
-Sky, time is running out!
Sky, let's go!
-So many cute guys!
-I'm here for clout!
-Girl, wait! For my profile pic.
-What time is it already?
Dear!
-Wow!
-Let's go now!
Dear!
It's Celeste!
-It's Celeste.
-Celeste.
-Are you ready?
-Celeste!
This is so cool. Is this real?
It's a secret.
What secret?
-It's really Celeste!
-Hi!
-Sis, I've missed you.
-Oh my God. What's your name?
Oh my God! We haven't seen
each other for so long.
Oh my God! You're so pretty now.
-Excuse me!
-Dear!
-She's beautiful, right?
-Such a beautiful nose!
-I don't know you guys!
-Yeah, who are you?
-It's Celeste!
-Oh my God!
-Let's just go.
-She's Celeste!
-No!
She's Celeste! She's my friend, right?
Oh my God! Whatever!
-Fabulous, right--
-Excuse me.
Would you like anything
to drink or eat, ladies?
I'll have the baked oysters
with special sauce.
I can't drink alcohol
because I'm pregnant.
-Got it.
-Yeah.
-And you, miss?
-Here's the payment.
I think I want a salad
and a margherita pizza.
-Okay, margherita pizza. Okay.
-Yes.
Dream on! What are you, nepo babies?
Kropek! I'll bring you kropek.
But kropek is on the house.
Good job!
Kropek!
Your dad only treats us once in a while,
but he's so stingy!
That's okay.
-You're not a rich kid. That's okay.
-We stole a lot today.
-You're a street rat!
-Just to experience it.
-Don't be picky!
-Girl, it's just once in a while.
Hello, Rosdan?
Don't worry, I will bring leftovers
for you and Riel.
Okay, Auntie Lena.
Love you, my favorite aunt!
Two sisig and…
Bano!
-You really get on my nerves!
-Come on.
You've been waking up
to this handsome face for 20 years.
You act like there's something new.
How's our daughter doing there?
Faye and Sky made a killing.
They hit the jackpot!
It's a lot.
A lot.
But…
I'm afraid of karma.
Karma, Lena?
Did we take the budget
of the flood control program?
-Bano!
-No.
If you see those party people…
You steal one watch from them,
they don't even care.
Tomorrow, they have ten more!
Us? If we lose this chance,
we'll have nothing, Lena.
Nothing at all!
Whatever we get tonight
will be enough for me to go to Qatar.
I promise.
This will be the last time.
This is the jackpot.
I'll go there.
What's up, Monsters?
Tonight…
-I won't let you go home sober!
-What an arrogant jerk!
Because all drinks are on me!
-My man!
-Sean!
You can't get his attention.
He's cute, in fairness.
All right, all right!
Up next on the stage,
we've got my girl,
DJ Elle!
-DJ Elle!
-You're like an animal!
You're staring too much at DJ Elle!
You're really so slow, James.
Why don't you just tell her
that you like her?
Yes, man.
Confess.
-Confess.
Crazy!
-DJ Elle!
-You two are truly siblings!
-Are you guys ready?
-Yes!
Yes, I like that!
-Let's all party to death!
-Yeah!
That's a lot of jewelry, girl.
Dear, I think you and I can do this.
Oh my God!
Target locked.
Do you see the jewelry, baby?
Sky, pause for now.
Why?
Let's enjoy the night.
No stealing. No scams.
Just like normal party-goers.
-Come on, for just a few minutes.
-Fine, go ahead.
-Please.
-You want some time for yourself, right?
Give this to me.
So that's why you're wearing
that kind of outfit.
Okay, go now. Fight!
-Thank you!
-Do your thing.
But for now, I'll strut my way there.
Look, baby, we're gonna steal from them.
Shush! Tone it down.
Let's go now.
There's a lot.
Hey, remember me?
You want to taste my Magic Mushroom?
What?
Thank you.
What about…
Sex on the Beach?
I mean…
the drink.
On the lookout for a new victim, Sean?
-How about you shut the fuck up, Marco?
-Hey!
Don't you dare talk
to my brother like that!
Just get out of here! You pervs!
Hey!
Pervs? Maybe she's asking for it.
-What?
-Get out of here!
How dare you! You, jerk!
I might even be bigger than you!
Oh my God!
We're not in the university.
Please don't make a scene here.
It was not me. It was him.
We know that you like this cat burglar.
What did you say?
Damn it. What?
-Stop!
-Stop it, Marco!
Stop it!
Stop fighting. You're causing trouble!
-Guard, get them!
-What?
-Guard, get that guy!
Let go of me! Come here!
-Come here!
-Why am I being dragged into this?
Faye!
-Come with me.
-Sky!
-Faye!
-Let's go!
-Me too?
-Yes, you too!
Take them!
I'm going, okay?
Guard, the hat!
Hey, what are you doing?
Shit.
Bummer!
Right now of all times?
Sir, the elevator is not working.
Is there another elevator here?
Let's go, love!
This way!
Hey!
Slow down, love.
Slow down.
I'll take care of this. Go!
What about Faye and Sky?
My love, find them.
Look for them.
I'll handle this. Go, quickly!
Go now! Find them!
Come on.
So hot.
Lights out now? Of all times?
What's happening?
-Look.
-It's so dark! And it's hot too!
-The pregnant woman's stressed. My god!
-Look, it's cute.
Marco, I want to go home.
I'm scared!
We'll go home once they get back.
When they get back, okay?
Damn it!
Why the hell did they lock us in here?
I'll deal with that.
Operation Lock-y Me.
-Faye and I got this.
-Excuse me.
Here, hold this.
There, push that part.
OMG! What are you, burglars? Carnappers?
We're not like you.
We had a lot to do just to survive.
Fine. Continue.
Arrogant! Don't mind her.
There. See? Perfect!
-See? We're good.
-Come now, Sky.
What happened? Are you okay?
-They're dead!
-Dead?
Who are they?
Everyone on the dance floor!
They're all dead!
Who's dead?
Wait.
-It's a prank!
-Yes, it's a prank.
-I saw it on a vlog. Who's vlogging now?
-Why is there…
Is that blood?
-No, it's not.
-Wait.
Maybe they're just drunk.
Guys.
People wearing masks.
What?
They were all killed!
-Believe me!
-Maybe someone's vlogging.
-What if she's telling the truth?
-I saw you drinking earlier.
Stop it!
-It's blood!
-No, it's not.
Believe me. I know blood.
I'm a vampire. Look.
What's that? Stop it!
Hey! That's not a funny joke.
-You have to believe me!
-You're just drunk.
They're all dead!
Ice?
Ice, are you okay?
Run! Let's go!
Sean, come on!
Marco!
Let's go! Hurry!
Let's go!
Downstairs!
Hurry!
Go.
Breathe.
Let's get out of here.
-Where are we going?
-Wait!
-Wait, let me think.
-Marco, don't go! I'm scared!
I don't want to die yet.
Where are we going to hide?
Marco!
Marco! Hurry up!
Be quiet!
I think they're gone.
Marco?
Marco!
Wait!
The DJ said everyone there is dead!
Why are we going back?
Let's see if there's an exit here.
That's what's important, okay?
Let's stay here, Faye.
-Stay here, please.
-Let's hide.
Hey!
Let's go! Stand up!
They're gone. Let's go!
Hurry! Or else, I'll leave you here.
Let's go!
Blood and soul will give him strength!
We will be his new aswang!
Come on.
Be careful!
Let's go now.
Come on! Hurry!
Who…
Who are those masked killers?
Maybe they're serial killers.
Members of a cult.
Cult?
It's 2025! There are still cults?
Cult members or serial killers,
the more important thing is
that we get out of here.
Wait, wait.
This looks like the design
in the dance area.
Prayers? Incantations?
Maybe the cult members
recite those before killing.
What? Are you crazy?
Why are you so obsessed
with cults? Stop it!
We're going to die here!
Mom?
Mom!
Where's Dad?
Faye.
Faye, we need to get out of here.
Let's go.
Breathe…
Hey!
Sky, are you okay?
We're going to die.
Thank you, my child.
Mom?
Could this be our karma?
I thought of that too, but…
If it's our karma,
why are they also affected?
What's happening?
Why are they trying to kill us all?
That's not important right now.
What's important right now…
is to be strong, right?
Elle, remember this.
We can't die here, okay?
We need to get out of here.
We need to find the exit.
Exit?
Wait.
The elevator…
That's the only way out.
How?
There's no electricity.
Basement 3. The electrical room is there.
Elle, can you and James go there?
Turn on the power supply
to operate the elevator.
But it would be easier
for the killers to locate us
if the electricity comes back.
They'll watch the elevator.
Wait.
What about my mom? She's hurt.
My child,
the important thing is for you and Sky
to get out of here immediately.
-Go.
-Mom, I won't leave you here.
We won't leave you.
You said that the family
that steals together stays together.
Okay. Here's what we'll do.
Elle, James, I'll lure them away
from the elevator.
Run to the electrical room,
then come back to the elevator.
We will wait for you in the lobby.
I've got this.
Guys, what's important is
that we do not lose hope.
We're already here.
We have nothing to lose.
That's why we must do this.
Be brave.
We can use these.
Get whatever you can use.
Let's go.
Sky, help her.
Ouch!
This came from
your great-great-grandmother.
This protected me from harm.
Now, this will protect you.
I'll come back for you, promise.
Mom, I'll come back for you.
Let's hurry!
Go now.
Help! I can't walk! Where are you?
Help! I can't walk!
Help!
Where are you? I'm lost! Help!
Fucker!
Let's go, Faye!
Let's go!
Be careful.
Elle, the switch!
-Don't leave me.
-Elle…
Don't leave me.
-Don't leave me.
-Stop crying.
The switch is what's important here, okay?
Stop crying. I'm just here, okay?
I'll take care of you.
Sky!
Why now?
Why didn't you kill us earlier?
Fear and panic…
That's just the appetizer.
But suffering,
betrayal,
despair…
That's fine dining.
Sweeter, more delicious.
All for the return of our lord!
And me,
I had fun watching you all run,
clinging to hope,
like a game.
But the game is over now.
Sean…
James and Elle, where are they?
Probably dead.
And you are my last course,
my final offering!
He is coming!
Faye!
Well, look who's still alive!
Run!
Let's go!
Sean!
Faye!
You want an offering?
Then you're the offering!
Die!
Sean!
Come on.
Sean, get up.
Let's go.
Sean.
Just a few more steps.
Sean, just a little bit more.
They killed my father.
And Sky.
If I'm going to die anyway,
I'd rather die on my own terms.
I give up.
Faye, don't say that.
Don't worry.
I'm just here. I'm not going to leave you.
We're together.
Where are Elle and James?
Move!
Callie!
Callie, please!
Damn you! Let go of my mother!
You, monster! Let go of my mom!
Mom!
You're lucky!
Tonight,
you will witness the return of our lord.
He is coming!
Let's go!
Quick!
Hurry, go inside!
Elle, you go with my mom.
Sean, let's go.
-Faye!
-Sean.
-Hurry up!
-Run!
Quick!
Hurry!
You can't escape!
You will all die!
And when our lord returns,
he will rule the world!
They're everywhere.
They attack anytime, day or night.
The whole world has turned its back on us.
There is no help coming.
When will this end?
Is there a way to end this?
I'm here!
There's nothing here.
We should have gone to the mall instead.
That's too far.
If you want, you can go by yourself.
We can find useful stuff there.
Hold this.
You know what?
All you think of is canned goods.
That would have been a waste.
A waste?
Let's go.
We can't be here after nightfall.
Dong, let's go!
Hold on.
Sir?
Let's go.
-Let's go!
-Run!
Hurry!
Faster, Dong!
Run!
Dong!
Dong, hurry!
Get up!
You went out again without these.
It's open.
No one's here.
Drea!
Auntie?
Auntie Malena!
-Where are you?
-Auntie?
Drea!
Auntie!
Dong?
Dong.
Open it.
-Drea!
-Dong!
-Dong.
-Drea.
-Auntie.
-What are you guys doing there?
Auntie.
Be careful.
Are you okay, Auntie?
What happened to you?
Did the oil in the bottles boil?
No.
Drea…
You only hide in there when the oil boils.
I thought something bad happened to you.
Next time,
lock the door.
Yes, Dong.
Dong.
You really went out for that?
Auntie…
Have some bean stew.
So we can at least feel Christmas…
Ho, ho, ho!
Merry Christmas!
Merry Christmas?
Dong.
Christmas isn't until next week.
I've got presents for you, guys.
My favorite canned meat is all yours.
Wow!
You love me more than food now.
It's a tie.
I love you both.
Thank you.
Riel.
For me?
That Swiss knife is newly sharpened.
Where did you get this?
You don't have to know.
This is cool.
Of course,
how could I forget?
Auntie.
I made this for you.
Thank you, Dong.
-Merry Christmas.
It's beautiful.
Dong.
Drea.
I'm sorry, we don't have gifts for you.
But…
I want to thank you.
Both of you.
Drea, thank you
for looking after Auntie.
Auntie Malena is like
a real grandmother to me, Rosdan.
We should be the ones
thanking your family.
Because
even though we are
in a difficult situation,
even with your situation,
you still accepted us wholeheartedly.
As long as we're together,
we'll make it.
We are a family.
Our conversation is getting too serious.
Let's celebrate!
-Merry Christmas!
Mia!
Rosdan!
You're having a nightmare.
You're having a nightmare, Rosdan.
Is it still about Mia?
If only I had done something to save her.
It's not your fault, Rosdan.
We know…
And I know that
you did everything to save her.
She still died, Riel.
All I can do now…
is make sure no one else in our family
falls victim to the aswang.
Dong, Riel.
Who are you?
I'm not your enemy.
-Then what are you doing here?
-I'm looking for someone.
Malena.
Malena Ocampo.
Don't move!
Where are your other companions?
They were killed by the aswang.
Why are you looking for Auntie Malena?
Because she's one of the survivors
of the Hellclipse Massacre.
October 31st, 2025.
Hellclipse?
What do you know about that?
That's where the aswang came from.
It wasn't the aswang that killed
those people at the party.
The organizers of Hellclipse
were a cult.
Worshippers of a monster
called Malum.
They slaughtered everyone at the party
to give Malum more strength,
so he could break free
from his prison, the chest.
What cult?
What chest?
-That's nonsense.
-Where did you hear all this?
My parents were part of the cult.
When they defected,
the aswang killed them.
With every kill,
Malum gets stronger.
I know where the chest is.
To stop Malum,
he must be returned there, locked away.
If Malum is defeated,
all the aswang will be defeated!
You have weapons here.
We can fight Malum.
We can fight Malum and the aswang.
You need weapons against the aswang?
Here.
You can go now.
You've planted plenty of sampana.
The aswang are afraid of that.
We are not marching into their territory!
We've been protecting each other
for a long time.
Do you think we will move carelessly?
Especially since I know that
we could be harmed.
Are you…
Malena Ocampo?
Who are you?
I just want to ask you something.
About what happened back in 2025--
Stop it!
We don't believe you.
My parents found this at the venue…
Faye.
Malena.
To end the evil,
you must return to where it all began.
Only our blood can defeat Malum.
Our family has
a deep connection with Malum.
Our family holds the answer.
End the curse.
-Auntie?
-Auntie!
-What did you do to her?
-Auntie, sit down.
Auntie. Get her some water.
-Auntie.
Auntie.
Please, leave us!
Rosdan.
Auntie.
We can't run away from him forever.
We can't run from him. Forever.
Who, Auntie?
Malum.
Our family can see and feel Malum.
-Malum?
-It's in our blood.
The power to stop him.
Just us.
Rosdan.
Dong! Auntie.
-Dong!
-Get Auntie out of here!
Drea! Run!
-Let's go!
-Quick!
Go with them.
Go with them!
Rosdan!
-Auntie! Come on, Auntie! Hurry!
-Auntie, Drea, go inside there!
Dong!
-Go!
-You first, Auntie!
Go inside!
Riel!
Let's go!
Quick!
Riel, get the car! Quick!
Go inside, Riel!
-Auntie!
-Hurry!
-We need to leave. Auntie!
-You go first!
-Go inside!
-Move!
You go inside, Riel!
Auntie, go inside now!
Go inside, you go first. Go first!
Auntie, come on! Auntie!
Come on!
Auntie.
What are you doing? Auntie!
Auntie! Auntie, come on!
You'll end this, Rosdan!
-Promise me you'll end this!
-Auntie!
Open this, Auntie!
Auntie!
-Get in!
-Rosdan!
Rosdan!
-Auntie!
-Rosdan!
-Rosdan, let's go!
-Auntie!
-Aswang!
Rosdan!
Let's go!
Hurry!
Let go!
Drea, come here!
What happened?
We ran out of gas.
-Rosdan.
-Hey, Rosdan.
Wait.
Why?
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
Here's water.
I think it's best if you leave now.
You may have been followed
and led trouble to us.
Friend, go outside now.
This is the map of the Hellclipse venue.
The chest is there.
Malum's there.
We survived today,
but what will happen to us next time?
Auntie is gone…
I don't know
how this fight of yours will end.
May God be with you.
-Rosdan!
-Thanks.
Let's go. I'll go with you.
Riel.
Look after Dong and Drea.
They need you here.
You think I can't fight?
That's why you don't want to take me?
You still think I'm a coward?
Rosdan, we have the same blood.
You're always the one saving me,
let me help you now!
Riel. That's not what I'm thinking.
So what is it?
Listen to me.
We don't know what's going to happen now.
But if only one of us can survive,
it should be you.
You understand me?
Are you trying to get yourself killed?
No, Riel.
We're fighting back.
-Dong!
-Run!
Riel!
Riel, go to Dong and Drea!
-Dong, let's go!
-Drea!
Hide! Hurry!
Dong!
Drea!
Drea, let's go! Hurry!
Go inside.
Riel, you go first!
Hurry!
It's Malum!
Run!
Come.
Riel.
Let's go.
-Drea.
-Dong, let's go!
Drea!
Riel!
Where's Dong?
Where's Drea?
Riel, where are they?
Riel!
Riel, both of you, leave now!
Rosdan!
Guys, be alert.
We don't know
the full extent of his abilities.
He's different from other aswang.
You…
will all die!
cannot stop me!
You will all die!
You cannot stop me!
Riel!
All of us have experienced
the loss of a loved one.
Parents. Siblings.
Spouses. Children.
Friends.
But in the midst of darkness,
we learned to fight back.
That strength was actually
within us all along.
No matter what happens,
we'll handle it.
The end of this remains uncertain,
but one thing is for sure.
As long as we live,
as long as there's hope,
even for a little,
we will not give up.